3712 Block Drive, 1148 Irving, TX 75038 (662) 347-0087 alexiservin92@gmail.com

ALEXIS ERVIN

SKILLS

I am a registered nurse with 4 years of nursing experience. I've worked in the following areas of nursing: hospital/acute care, home-health, case management and psychiatric. I have current unexpired certifications in Basic Life Support and Advanced Cardiovascular Life Support. I have a Texas RN Compact license with no restrictions to practice as registered nurse.

EXPERIENCE

Home Health Professionals - RN Case Manager

January 2018- present

- Hospice registered nurse: provide palliative nursing care to patients with terminal diagnoses.
- Duties/Responsibilities: pain/symptom management related to dying process, manage LVNs and hospice Aides involved in patient care, advocate for patient/family, work as member of an interdisciplinary team to provide individualized plan of care.

First Baptist Medical Center, Dallas, TX - Contract RN/Acute Care Nurse

August 2017- December 2017

- Provide nursing care in hospital setting according to Texas Board of Nursing practice laws
- Follow physician's orders for post-op bariatric patients
- Provide skilled care for patients immediately following recovery from PACU
- Nursing skills: central Line care/removal, PICC line care/removal, IV therapy, nursing process, Foley catheter insertion/removal, JP drain care, patient nutritional education

Pinnacle Senior Care, Irving, TX - RN Case Manager/ Field Nurse

July 2016 - July 2017

- Provided skilled nursing care to patients in the home setting.
- Assessed patients' medical and psychosocial needs to create care plans accordingly.
- Communicated with supervisor, physical therapists, and social workers to meet patients' needs and physician's orders.
- Educated patients on ways to prevent exacerbations of chronic diseases to prevent hospitalization.

TruStaff Travel Agency, Dallas-Fort Worth, TX -Contract/Travel RN

- Assigned to Richland Hills Hospital as an acute care nurse.
- Floated to various units as requested by supervisors:
 Medical-Surgical Unit, Progressive Care Unit and Emergency Department.
- Length of Contract: 13 weeks.

Chicot Memorial Medical Center, Lake Village, AR -Special Care RN

FEBRUARY 2015 - FEBRUARY 2016

- Provided hands-on nursing care to patients with critical medical conditions.
- Assessed patients and provided plan of care in accordance to physician orders. Comply with federal HIPPA standards.
- Specialty area: Telemetry, Medical-Surgical, Progressive Care.

Delta Regional Medical Center, Greenville, MS -Staff RN

JULY 2014- JANUARY 2015

- Provided hands-on nursing care to patients on a medical-surgical/ pediatric unit.
- Supervised LVNs/CNAs and developed individualized care plans for each patient.
- Occasionally provided care to toddlers and school-age children.

EDUCATION

University of Texas at Arlington - In Progress (RN to BSN to MSN Degree)

Alcorn State University, Lorman, MS - Associate of Nursing Degree
AUGUST 2012 - May 2014, Alcorn State School of Nursing

 $\begin{tabular}{ll} \textbf{Mississippi State University, Starkville, MS} &-\textit{Pre-Requisites for} \\ \textit{nursing school} \end{tabular}$

SEPT. 2010- JULY 2012

LICENSE/ CERTIFICATIONS

- *Texas RN Compact License*, (Texas Board of Nursing): License# 913151 (Active)
- Basic Life Support, (American Heart Association) July 2017- July
- Advanced Cardiovascular Support (American Heart Association) Nov. 2017- Nov. 2019